foxsoccer.tv 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy | Help | FOX Soccer 2Go

**FOX Soccer 2Go Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date: February 8, 2016**

**1.INTRODUCTION**

Fox Soccer Channel LLC ("Fox Soccer" or "we" or "us") operates the FOX Soccer 2Go (previously, FoxSoccer.tv) website [http://www.foxsoccer2go.com](http://www.foxsoccer2go.com/) ("FOX Soccer 2Go" or "Site"), which is an online platform that allows Members to purchase and stream live soccer and rugby matches. The services offered by Fox Soccer include online premium subscription services, newsletters, mobile alerts and any other features, content, or applications offered from time to time by Fox Soccer in connection with Fox Soccer's business (collectively, the "FOX Soccer 2Go Services"). Fox Soccer is part of the United States based operations of Twenty-First Century Fox, Inc.

As set forth in our [Terms of Use](http://www.foxsoccer2go.com/terms), FOX Soccer 2Go is a general audience website, is not targeted to children, and does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. 

This Privacy Policy describes Fox Soccer's collection, use and sharing of personal information about users (e.g., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name, email address and financial information) where that personal information is not otherwise publicly available on the Site. This Privacy Policy also describes generally Fox Soccer's practices for handling non-personally identifiable information (e.g., user interests, demographics, or Site usage) to the extent such non-personally identifiable information is associated with a particular user or user account. This Privacy Policy applies to all "users," including both visitors (users who use some of the Site Services without being registered with Fox Soccer), "Members" (users who have registered with Fox Soccer) and "Subscribers" (Members who have purchased an online premium subscription). 

**2.SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION ON WEBSITE**

_User Submitted Information_

**Account Registration Information** is the required information that a Member must provide to us when they initially register on the Site (by creating a "user account") and includes first name, last name, email address and password. You must create a user account in order to purchase an online subscription or sign up for newsletters or mobile alerts.

**Online Video Subscription Information**. If you elect to purchase any online video subscription through the Site in addition to providing the Account Registration Information mentioned above you will also be required to provide personal financial information, including your credit card number, billing address or other payment information (collectively, "Personal Financial Information") to the third party service provider selected by Fox Soccer to provide payment services for the Site. At the time of purchase you will also be requested to select your video subscription type (e.g. Monthly or Annual). **Your online video subscription will be automatically renewed and the credit card you used to subscribe for such online video subscription will be charged per the billing cycle of your selected online video subscription (e.g. Monthly or Annual), unless you cancel the online video subscription prior to the renewal date of your online video subscription**. If you have any questions about canceling your online video subscription or our refund policy, please refer to our [Terms of Use](http://www.foxsoccer2go.com/terms). You must be 18 years of age or older to submit Personal Financial Information on the Site, including to place an order on the Site. 

_Site Collected Information_

**Site Activity Information**. When users visit the Site, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Site, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the FOX Soccer 2Go Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, geolocation data, or other transactional information for that device in order to serve content to it. 

We also may use cookies and other tracking technologies (including browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe flash technology including cookies), which are small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites, apps and services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that website. We may use these technologies to collect and store information about your usage of the Site, such as pages you have visited, search queries you have run, and advertisements you have seen. We also collect personal information in manual or off-line format, such as a post card or subscription form. Providing a detailed privacy policy in those situations is often impractical. In these situations, we will provide consumers with a short notice that describes how to obtain the full text of this Privacy Policy.

Third-parties that support the Site by serving advertisements or providing FOX Soccer 2Go Services, such as allowing users to purchase and view online video subscriptions or tracking aggregate Site usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. Fox Soccer does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. For more information about third party ad networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info/consumers](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers), and to opt-out of such ad networks' and services' advertising practices, go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).You may download the AppChoices app at [www.aboutads.info/appchoices](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices) to opt-out in mobile apps.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., [http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies)).Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe's website, see [http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html](http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html).Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features or personalization available through FOX Soccer 2Go Services.

**Third Parties**. To improve the quality of the FOX Soccer 2Go Services, we may supplement the information we collect with information that is collected or provided by third parties. If you access the FOX Soccer 2Go Services through a third party connection or log in, we may also collect your user ID and/or user name associated with that third party service, or any information you have made public in connection with that service and which the third party shares with partner services.

**3. **NOTICE & CHOICE****

**Means of Notice and Choice.** This Privacy Policy is the primary means by which Fox Soccer provides you with notice and choice regarding its collection and use of your personal information. Fox Soccer will not use your personal information in a manner different from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your permission. 

**Privacy Policy Changes.** Fox Soccer may modify this Privacy Policy as necessary. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that expand our rights to use your personal information, we will notify you to seek your consent either through an email or a prominent posting on the Site.

**Linked Websites.** FOX Soccer 2Go Services may also be linked to websites operated by Fox Soccer affiliates (i.e., that are part of the Twenty-First Century Fox, Inc.: "Affiliated Companies") or third parties. FOX Soccer 2Go is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave FOX Soccer 2Go Services via a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third-party site. Additionally, although all Affiliated Companies adhere to the Twenty-First Century Fox corporate Privacy Principles, users who visit an Affiliated Company website should still refer to the Affiliated Companies' separate privacy policy, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites that do not display or link to this Privacy Policy or have their own privacy statements.

**Collection of Personal Financial Information by a Third Party.** At the time of your purchase, Fox Soccer will notify you of the identity of any third party that is collecting, transmitting, storing and/or processing your Personal Financial Information. **You acknowledge and agree that this Privacy Policy will not apply to any Personal Financial Information that you provide to any independent third party company on the Site and that all payment obligations related to such purchase shall be governed solely by the applicable independent third party company's privacy policy. You further acknowledge and agree that Fox Soccer will have no liability for or responsibility for such independent third party company's use or protection of your Personal Financial Information**. You should check the privacy policy of the independent third party company's website to determine how it will handle any Personal Financial Information it collects from you and/or processes. You acknowledge and agree that in the event that such independent third party company experiences a data breach that compromises or otherwise affects your Personal Financial Information, Fox Soccer shall in no way be responsible or liable to you for such breach. You should contact the applicable independent third party company regarding any such data breach.

**4\. USE & DISCLOSURE**

 _

_Fox Soccer's Use and Disclosure of Information_

_

We only share your non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe the sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy. In addition, Fox Soccer may share your personal information with Affiliated Companies.

We use the information you provide us for the following purposes:

**To provide and manage the FOX Soccer 2Go Services**. We use the information we collect from and about users to provide the FOX Soccer 2Go Services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content and marketing messages, and to provide you with customer support and enable you to respond to inquiries. We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on the FOX Soccer 2Go Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**To allow third party service providers to assist us in providing and managing the FOX Soccer 2Go Services.** Fox Soccer may make your non-public personal information available to certain third-party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide FOX Soccer 2Go Services by, for example: developing or supporting products and the FOX Soccer 2Go Services; fulfilling online video subscription orders; collecting, and processing Personal Financial Information; or processing data or statistics. These third-party service providers are required to protect non-public personal information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing to you and Fox Soccer. 

**To deliver relevant content and recommendations.** To make your experience more interesting, we may use any of the information you provide, the information we collect about your page views and queries, and information we may collect from other users and third parties to assist us in recommending content on FOX Soccer 2Go.

**To contact you.** Fox Soccer may periodically send promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or correspondence related to the FOX Soccer 2Go Services to the email address you provided to us at registration. If you want to stop receiving correspondence from Fox Soccer, you can click on the "Update Personal Details" link under "[My Account](https://secure.foxsoccer2go.com/my-account)," or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to the FOX Soccer 2Go Services or policies.

**To protect the rights of FOX Soccer 2Go and our users.** There may be instances when Fox Soccer may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where Fox Soccer has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of Fox Soccer, our Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the FOX Soccer 2Go Services or members of the public including responding to emergencies where there appears to be a danger of death or injury to any person; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with applicable laws, rules and regulations ("Applicable Laws") or legal process. 

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If Fox Soccer sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Fox Soccer may transfer your user information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**5\. SECURITY**

Fox Soccer uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard user information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.

**6\. ACCESS, REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE**

**User Control and Account Cancellation.** Through the My Account option, you can access and edit your account registration information. If you no longer want to use the FOX Soccer 2Go Services, you may deactivate your user account by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link on the My Account function. When you deactivate your account you will no longer have access to the online video subscription service. We may retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after deactivation for fraud detection or to comply with Applicable Laws or our internal security policies.

 ** **

**CONTACT US**

****

********If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Fox Soccer at:

Email:   

Mail: 

FOX Soccer 2Go Privacy Officer  
c/o Fox Cable Networks Services, LLC  
Business and Legal Affairs  
P.O Box 900  
Beverly Hills, California 90213-0900

Telephone:  
(310) 369-1350
